applause
calm (at sea)
Are you free later tonight?
Would you like to go out with me?
I've always wanted to talk to you.
Still a chatting party after the rain
heave, ho!
Talking in the rain while it's raining
L'xei
non-stop talking
Yes, good evening to all of you who are watching YouTube LIVE Amefurasshi Official Channel.
Good evening.
We are Amefurasshi.
Best regards.
Yes, Moeka was in charge this time.
Yes, I have read Issa-san.
The episode of the sleepover, which was the first place in the "Yakkashi" episode, was told in a funny way, but it was a good story that made me cry because I could feel the bond between the members.
Thanks to you, I had a lot of fun at Amefurasshi this year.
Thank you so much for keeping it going.
I was very happy to see that you wrote "Let's just have fun," and I appreciate your comment that you think people will want to see it too.
Thank you very much.
For the title call, "I've always wanted to talk to you," we will choose one of the people who tweeted their impressions of Ameshabe and call out his or her name.
Yeah.
Please tweet us your thoughts on the program with Ameshabe.
Please.
What's wrong?
What is it?
It's cold.
What's wrong?
Too cold with terminal cold.
Not the end.
Let me do it here today.
I can't see your face.
It's cold.
Are you okay?
I bought a turtleneg for the first time in my life.
Definitely not.
It doesn't look like yuzu.
I bought it for the first time in my life, didn't know how to use it, and just looked it up on Google. How to use it?
You're definitely just going to wear it, that's all.
Yes.
, ,
I'm sorry, today. Please don't. Please don't say it. It's all right.
So you are all right? Yes, I am.
This is how I would like to go today. Today. Yes.
Did you cut your hair, Mr. Suzuki? I did.
I cut it off with a tortoise. Live specs? For Shinagawa.
Is it for live performance? Yes, we do.
A little bit of Mr. San, too. I'm letting the color fade for Shinagawa.
The color is very faded. It's so bright. Oh no. It's dirty.
And Hoshio? I am always in line as usual.
So you are saying that you have not prepared anything. No, no, I am just before.
It seems like it's a bit last minute, though. Oh no, only 4 more days, right? It's not good.
Well, we participated in various festivals and events last weekend, but first of all, we would like to thank you for your support.
What, yesterday? Yesterday, GalaFest was yesterday. I performed at GalaFest yesterday.
I don't know what the date feels like, but thank you very much for allowing me to perform at GalaFest every year.
Was yesterday our first venue? Yes! Hibiya Ongakudo. I think it was our first time.
I've never known such a slippery place before. I had never heard of such a slippery place. But it is famous, isn't it? I heard so. Yes, I found out about it yesterday.
He asked me to be careful before I left.
More than you can imagine,
I really slipped and almost didn't dance. I almost didn't dance.
I really felt bad for showing such a lack of dancing. The fly-out was too tight.
Hey, I thought. I can't step on it at this time, so during the chorus. I was dancing, wondering what to do.
I can't do it at all. Oh, I see. So you are stepping on it then. Yes, I am. Normally, I'm holding on. I put a lot of effort into it.
It was a version that was impossible and not a stomping ground. It was.
I was taking the dorky dorky version with me. That was the dorky-dorky version.
But it was around evening when you left peacefully. I was just thinking about it.
This was beautiful, the psyllium and all. Yes, it was beautiful.
I'm really curious. My voice is muffled.
I'm a loud guy, so I think it's just fine. Yes, that's right. I'm usually a little loud.
I was thinking of easing up. Then a little louder, please, today.
I don't want to be told by Kojima, day in and day out. He's all cozy.
I was surprised. I always turn up the volume when I listen to flowers. That's right.
I'll lower it when I'm in England. So I think, I can't hear myself.
So every time I spoke louder, but every time I couldn't be heard.
It's tiny. It's a tiny thing. I feel big about it.
Yes.
Well, but I did it for the first time at that swell venue,
I was with Reni-chan.
And what's more, we were in the same dressing room. He was so cute!
It was cute, like a snowman. I don't know, the white outerwear wasn't cute. Hey, it was super cute.
Winter girls. Private clothes, that one.
Isn't it? Cute. Super cute.
Did I let you meet him?
I'm done.
You know, properly, we call it Amefurasshi Juice.
Then he looked kind of awkward. Like, "Don't be so formal about it.
I know that I know.
Yeah, it was like I already knew.
It was so cute.
What did you talk about?
Oh, but if Renni-chan had asked me to take care of Okinawa, and I had said please, I would have been a little...
Problem?
The problem, I was really wondering if this was a good idea. I had a thought.
Something like that, Ichikawa-san turned 20 this November, right?
And you said that if I were to make a toast with my seniors, I would like to toast first with Arline, who has been a great help to me, right?
You said.
Yesterday, Ichikawa-san said himself that he would like to have a drink with me.
Oh, man.
Significance.
I'm saying.
From myself.
Oh, Folk Village? There was, wasn't there, the other day?
The other day, the one with the flowers.
Yes. Hana was the performer from Flash, and she sent me a message during the rehearsal,
Aryn told me that Yuzuki wanted to drink alcohol, and I asked her if she wanted to drink alcohol. Aaron said, "Yuzuki wants to drink alcohol, so I'm going to drink alcohol,
Then he told me to drink on my own.
Aryn-like.
I received the transformation at Folk Village and decided to drink it on my own.
Aaryn was angry.
You were angry, I'm sure.
He was so mad.
Because I think Arline really wanted to drink.
Sorry, sorry.
Arline is such,
I thought it meant bad.
I don't think you are attached to me enough to be that angry.
Why don't you just drink it on your own?
I'm glad, something about you being that pissed off for me.
They didn't seem to care very much.
Right?
But, but,
I thought it was. It's Arline.
It's okay, it's Aryn, okay, that's it.
Isn't that the beauty of Arline?
Yes, that's right.
It's very Aryn-esque, isn't it?
Then with Aaryn, I said I wanted Aaryn first,
Are you and Leni going to lose together?
So I took a bite between rehearsals of the singing contest.
I'm not stupid, absolutely not.
Absolutely not.
Excuse me, can I just have a sip?
Aaryn.
I said okay.
If you want, you could take a throwaway shot or something, that's what I'd do.
It doesn't.
That's not true.
That's as good as it gets.
So, what's it like? You're in for a treat, aren't you, Mr. Ichikawa?
Arline and Andmate by myself.
I wanted to drink first.
It is.
That's disrespectful to Leni-chan.
Because that's what it is.
I mean, you, you're in good trouble.
What?
The two senior members of the team are mocking each other, saying, "Which one of us is responsible for this?
That's pretty bad.
You said it too, when you were pigeonholed.
I want to drink with Kanako, but I want to drink with Arline first,
You said it when you were a hatchet man, you.
It's bad, you too, really.
Hmm?
But I'm not drinking.
We don't even have a chance to meet.
You just couldn't meet, that's all.
I couldn't do it.
I just didn't know how to contact them.
No, Yu-chan will cheat you. You're the worst.
Yes, because I am the worst.
Watch out! Thank you, thank you. I was almost fooled.
Soon, they put me on a road car.
Scary.
No, you can't.
But you never know. There's also the possibility that those who don't wake up won't be able to make the toast.
Yes, that's right.
Maybe.
But Leni also said let's have a toast.
I'm not sure.
Because he gave me a hand.
I don't know.
He gave me a hand.
I made sure to take a video of it.
But there are no flowers.
Why?
I will not allow them to be present.
After all, I don't want to do anything that will cause misunderstanding, after all, I am 20 years old.
Soft drinks.
He said if he did it, he would go to the ants to shoot or something.
I understand.
Before I go any further, I send you a toast to Leni-chan.
I understand. I will send it.
If it's too much trouble for ants, it's ants. I don't care.
Play.
Have fun.
That is the beauty of ants.
Cute.
I'm trying to get by with that.
True.
But I say something.
Ants.
Ali, you know, I love that he is so savvy.
I see.
It makes me happy that they are treating me like a friend.
Oh, he said, I'm doing it.
I felt like they recognized me as a friend if they said it was okay, rather than if they just said it was fine.
That's great. I denied all of Mr. Takagi. Now.
No, but, no, Mr. Takagi is surprisingly very close to me.
Yes. But it's just because of the yuzu and the, uh, and the guessing.
Yes. We get nervous and become like this. It's just that we are like this.
Leni, you come pretty close.
Yeah. Yeah.
Concern.
Well, that's all then.
Unless you guys are too nervous. No, but that's a guess, so I can't do that.
Guess, you know, I get really nervous. It's different, guess what.
That's right. It's really different.
I don't know, but I'm looking forward to the report, right? Right, Chika?
Enjoy. Which one did you take?
Ailin or Lerye? Wow, which one did you choose?
So, if Lely and Aylin kissed, we could have indirectly toasted together.
What are you talking about? Really.
I don't understand. I really don't get it.
Lery tutu. And.
I will enjoy it. Yes, I will.
I wanted super high quality, camera of the day. 4K.
4K: It sucks.
I watched it once, and even Kojima definitely wears very little makeup. I wear makeup, all the time.
Kojima, you always wear ameshabe, so your makeup is a little light today.
That's right. It's just thin and proper.
Something. I'm trying to get out as much as I can.
Live?
You mean it's different from the live makeup?
That's because you don't wear live makeup.
No, usually.
I'm not a wraith.
There are times like that, aren't there? Yeah, I know.
Yuzu is always dressed up and made up.
Look, I have all of these brand new, today.
It just happened today, didn't it? No, sir.
No, it is not.
Yuzu is the most enthusiastic.
I wanted to give my skin a rest before my one-man show.
I see. That's how it's done.
Yuzu is the best,
Maybe they have cute clothes. Me, I think.
Yes, it is.
Always the same clothes. Here.
Always the same clothes.
I think you always wear denim with holes in it.
That's why I bought a new one.
I decided it was time to buy.
It's a whole body.
I bombed it with a core.
But sure, the shoes are cute today.
Did you change the whole body?
Stop, stop.
I quit.
I've never seen it before.
Yes.
It was some kind of core and cheap,
These shoes are also expensive because ag's are too expensive,
I made it to the core.
Fake.
You can buy it.
I can't buy it.
I can't afford it, ag is super expensive.
Always ask your dad.
Seriously, really.
Listen, to my parents the other day,
Nothing lately, of course, because I'm this old,
It's normal that they don't buy it,
I couldn't afford it,
It's Christmas or birthday time,
Because I want things,
Please, I said, just buy one top,
It was no good.
It didn't work.
Run away.
That's how much they buy.
When I said, "That's about as good as it gets,
What are you talking about?
Me.
It's new. And you have a job.
Age 21.
Well, at this age,
They may not buy much.
I don't think I should ask for it.
It's gone.
From high school, I haven't been hit yet.
That's right.
And the older brother, oh my.
Big brother is good because he's blender-ish.
I hope you're away. I'll give it to you. Give me all the New Year's money I want.
Give me. Shin-chan, give it to me.
I'm jealous of people who have a lot of relatives. I don't have many relatives.
I can't turn around at all. Even though I say I have many relatives in Ishikawa, I have many cousins, younger cousins, so they take everything.
So we are the ones who have to give, right? I've been giving since I graduated from high school.
When you have younger people. When you're younger, you know. Well, they're cute. You don't owe them anything. I'll never give it to you, Mr. Hanada.
I won't give it to you. But I'm sure you'd be happy with Big Thunder or something.
Big Thunder? I've always had a box of Big Thunder from my dad's sister?
Did we start talking about Disney? I only have a Disney head.
Big Thunder, or Black Thunder. Black Thunder.
Black Thunder. Big Thunder Mountain is so bad.
I was going to Disney too much. Good for both of us.
I was given a box of Black Thunder as a New Year's gift. The whole box.
Wouldn't you be happy with that? That's very nice.
He wants to give me a box of Karpas or something. I understand.
Soon after all the story will be out of the way and you will be the sister of the food family.
It money is a misunderstanding. I was talking about Galafest at first.
That's right. What do you want to talk about?
He said he enjoyed the Gala Fest. It was fun, wasn't it?
Thank you for your hard work.
We had rehearsals and went to Shinagawa Stella Goal, and the lessons are progressing very well.
I've been pointley today.
What day are you going? Tomorrow, four days from now?
Oh no, we're running out. I want to go through it 10 more times. It's really bad.
But that's a secret. Dreams are broken. It ain't gonna break.
But we're going to make it 100 until the day of the event. That's right. Even 20 today. That's great. You said 20 on Monday.
Not yet, to be honest. Not quite there. I'm trying to get through.
The more I let them through, the more anxious I get. I want to be pushed to the very edge like that.
I also started to wonder if this was really the right thing to do. After trying it, I see. So there are things you can understand.
I have been doing a lot of the standard things that I thought would be exciting in the past, so I always end up doing the same things that I thought would be exciting,
There are many new challenges this time, so I was worried about whether the event would be exciting or not.
It's the SASUKE down the middle, isn't it? You are challenging SASUKE. Yes, you challenge and hit the ball right there.
Even if. Even if.
A long time ago. A long time ago.
It's live.
I was like, "I'm not sure if it's okay to be here.
Challenge.
It lowers the leg ball, really.
Everyone is taking it very seriously, and because everyone wants everyone to really enjoy it, the more I think about it, the more I am unsure of the right answer.
Are you saying that's not true to the fullest?
That's not true.
Great answer.
I think it's a great answer.
That's right.
That is also important.
But true.
But something definitely.
From here.
I'm sure it will be a fun concert, of course.
Yes, of course.
It's our confidence building, the rest is up to us.
I'll be fine. I'll be perfect by the show.
You'll gain confidence.
If we do it with confidence.
Yes.
Sort of.
There is an element of uncertainty, though.
A little bit, really, because there's something new.
I'm nervous, already.
I'm just nervous.
Now I am more anxious.
I'm anxious. But I will definitely entertain you.
Yeah.
Why?
Look forward to it.
Yes.
Yes, that's why.
This will be the last Ameshabe this year.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
So we have been here every day this year.
It's coming, isn't it?
I would like to look back on everything in this section for the year 2023.
I see.
Here we go.
Se.
The Amefurasshi 2023 Review Special.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Yes! This is a well-known corner where we present the top 10 funniest episodes of Amefurashi in a ranking style,
We would like to make a top 10 list to review in 2023.
It can be a totally group topic, private, or personal.
I see.
But, you know, if we proceed at our usual pace, the first place will be announced next year,
Oh no. Let's start a little early and quickly announce the top 10.
Yes.
10th.
I'm going to read a little spacha.
Thank you, Mr. Toi.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Shimiyu.
Thank you, Nao.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Shimotoro.
Thank you, Kosuke.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Kaju.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Satsuo-san.
Thank you, Mr. Naito.
Thank you very much.
Kazuyuki, I have a question for you.
Thank you all.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. A lot.
Then, 10th place.
Let's roll it up and roll it up.
But, you know, a lot of things really happened this year.
That's right.
Isn't it difficult?
I wrote it down.
Isn't this it? This one. This is No. 10.
It's out of the province.
No, no, no, no, that's out of state.
What? What? What?
Because there are more than 10 of them out there, right? Then it's out of the prefecture.
Then first.
No. Out of state?
Then go ahead and announce out-of-prefecture.
10th.
A big case of candyfloss.
The big event?
Hammarl-chan's big unveiling.
Out-of-prefecture, out-of-state.
Yay.
Yes, I am.
Hamster, Hammar-chan
I have a
That's more than a year, I think,
I hid it from everyone.
Fans, of course.
He hid it from the members, and they hid it from him.
Actually, for about a year now.
I'd like to report that I had a hamster.
I was able to do it, and it was very
Hey, wow 2023.
Just because it's hidden doesn't mean it's ew.
It's not going to grow.
You were surprised, that's when.
I want to hide it.
There was no point in hiding it.
Yes, there is. Yes, there is.
I don't know. I don't know.
I started putting it out the moment I figured it out.
I hid it a little at first.
But if you're going to hide it this well,
I've been trying to hide it for a long time,
Is that why you hid it?
First time,
I was scared of the idea of keeping animals,
Thrilled,
He ran away.
Oh yeah, like a few months or something.
When they are gone,
In the morning, good morning,
There were cases where we would pile them up and crush them.
That's what I was afraid of,
I have no idea how to do it.
It's a first.
At first I thought I'd hide it for a few months,
If you want to hide it for a few months like that,
I've been trying to hide it for a long time,
I hid it for a long time.
I really think, Moeka is strange.
It's weird.
It's really different.
If you hide it that well, you hide it.
They don't hide it in the first place.
I understand.
And I know it makes you feel uneasy,
I know you don't tell that to your fans,
I don't see the point in hiding it from the members.
Indeed.
I could have known if I went to the house.
If you come to stay over,
It's not like I want to know.
After I said that much and left.
I was kind of suspicious,
When I went to the house,
Lies.
Why not?
So there were two of us.
Are you going to try to lie at the end?
I thought that would be interesting.
It's different.
No one spends this kind of time on Maru Hanyu.
I'm out of the prefecture.
It's over.
We did it! We won 10th place.
They are growing up so cute.
Then I'm glad.
Please continue to show us how you have grown.
Look forward to it.
Okay, let's go with #10.
It can't be helped.
If I can't get in, I'll go down.
It will be lowered.
You said you've always been fine with that.
In 10th place.
Poor Manmaru.
I guess it's 9th place.
It's important, Manmaru-chan.
It's all up there.
This and this.
As a grandfather.
All I see is moe.
10th.
Is it important?
Reunited with Grandpa.
That's 10th place, that's it.
It's Amerash 2023.
Also in 2023 in Moeika.
Grandpa.
My grandpa lives in Hokkaido, so it's hard for me to see him.
How long has it been since you've seen him?
Like, for the first time since elementary school.
I haven't seen him very much.
It's been a crazy long time since we met.
My grandfather came to my house.
I said, "Grandpa, it's been a long time,
He said, "Nice to meet you.
I thought he was a joking old man.
I thought it was a joke.
What are you talking about? I said, "What are you talking about?
Then,
His brother's wife came down.
When it comes,
I felt that my brother's wife was a moeka.
I came down from Moeika.
If I did it like I was my grandfather's wife,
I was seriously saying it was nice to meet you.
Her hair color and other things have changed a lot.
I don't know that she's blonde.
You certainly wouldn't know it from elementary school.
So,
At first I wondered what he was talking about,
I thought he was serious.
I seriously made a mistake.
Haven't you seen your grandkids in action or something?
I don't know about grandpa.
SNS.
Are you on line with Grandpa?
That's another grandpa.
Grandpa over there,
I'll have them send you a line.
Very much.
The other one will never be read.
Elementary or middle school,
If I send you a picture like I graduated,
I couldn't get a read on it for the rest of my life.
I couldn't get a read on it after all these years.
If any,
I was using an account, so I was on line.
It was like, why was that there?
He is such a useless old man.
Cute.
But it was wrinkled,
I touched a lot of wrinkles.
Is that so?
He said it was wrinkled.
His earlobes are huge, too, Grandpa.
He said, "Your earlobes are amazing," and touched them a lot.
Isn't that a baby?
Out-of-Prefecture.
It was out of the prefecture.
Thank you very much.
If we don't do this, now.
If more than that comes in,
All you have to do is put down both of them.
In 9th place for now.
9th for now.
Flushed, something.
Tentative.
8th, right?
8th.
Karuizawa-chan.
It's too thin for me personally.
I'll tell you what.
8th place, please.
Karuizawa Jike.
Karuizawa.
I don't say much.
Didn't you go to Karuizawa?
Actually, I will be performing in Karuizawa.
Don't.
Everyone is a liar today.
With friends,
All my friends,
There was a bit of a struggle.
What?
Group?
First time,
There was a struggle in the group.
It's my first fight.
It's like a fight, like a tight, wow,
I don't want it anymore, like, not like,
It's kind of awkward for everyone,
It's kind of a blur, that's about it.
The air has gone bad.
There were days when it seemed like the air got a little bad.
But I don't know why,
That night,
We all went together.
Why?
I don't know why,
That's not bad air.
But what can I say?
We didn't fight.
It was just a blur, a little bad air.
And when I went to the public bathhouse,
Everyone was naked together,
It was like, "Let's say what we want to say,
So there,
Like, this is not like this, this is not like that.
So, neatly resolve it together,
We were actually going to play everyone in pieces, but the next day.
I thought, "Let's all play together now,
All the girls,
Go to Karuizawa,
Amazing.
I took a trip to Karuizawa, a day trip,
All of my friends have a vacation home in Karuizawa,
is?
All kinds of amazing.
And Karuizawa is amazing for a day trip,
And Karuizawa for a day trip.
I have a vacation home, and that's it,
All my friends drove me,
Drive there,
I was planning to go home at night,
Something,
I was really into Netflix's Mask Girl at the time,
I only plan to watch one episode,
I've seen it all,
I watched it while eating samgyapsal or something,
Samgyapsal.
While eating at the villa,
I saw a masked girl.
It ended up being a very late night,
I left, around morning.
It's great, it's fulfilling.
December was also spent.
We've sold it downtown.
And friends who have vacation homes,
Some of them.
What's that?
It's not a big one.
Just having it is amazing.
Mr. Ishikawa, the rich man?
No, no.
Mr. Ishikawa,
I don't have the most money in this group.
What are you talking about?
But that's really true, isn't it?
Well, let me tell you.
The richest person who has the most.
I really don't have it.
Because,
My house, that's it.
That one, right?
I don't know why.
The level of family complexity,
That's not true.
If anything, it's lovey-dovey.
We are good friends,
Nothing like that,
You're not two people earning two people.
So, that's great.
What are you talking about?
It's amazing how many people have vacation homes.
True, both of us.
Trees, it seems like everyone has them itro.
I want to rent a villa.
It's okay, I think so.
It's okay.
Gentle.
Someone has to be able to drive.
If you can drive,
With driver.
Put a driver on.
I can get you a driver as well.
It's okay.
Follow us.
I would like to do so.
I want to live.
Ishikawa, in fact, was rich.
Finally.
Finally out.
Do we need to talk about Univa?
Univa should also be in 8th place.
The other is,
Next day,
I had a reservation to play with all my friends,
Where are you going the day before?
I was talking about something like,
The day to schedule,
Time was really slow with everyone's rules,
At about 1:00 am,
What do we do tomorrow?
We were talking about something like that.
It's today.
Today, even if Tokyo,
It was raining.
I really hate playing in the rain.
Don't you hate playing in the rain?
When it was like,
It was sunny in Osaka.
He said, "It's sunny in Osaka,
To Univa,
Decide to go at 1 or 2 am,
Leave at about 4:00 in the morning,
Fly to Osaka,
It was cheaper to fly.
What?
From Shinkansen.
Were you from a rich family?
No, no, no.
Flying is cheaper than the bullet train.
He said I am taking the night bus.
Did you take the night bus?
It was until midnight. The night bus.
I really wanted to take the night bus,
There was no night bus,
The power of action is amazing.
Go by plane with all,
I went straight home on the night bus.
Morning. The next morning.
I was at Univa the same day,
By chance.
Because we're off together.
Now you're going to Univa?
I got a line and thought, what is this guy talking about?
It was at a time when it seemed like you would never be able to come.
If you go to Univa,
I was like, "Oh, yeah.
Find it,
What's he doing?
Really, because my schedule was pretty packed at the time.
You were just in time?
It was off I did it.
The next day, you come back in the morning if it's an overnight bus,
I slept again in the evening.
Oh no.
There definitely is. I want to sleep. I want to sleep.
I knew I had the power to take action.
I want to sleep.
And.
It's amazing.
This is a private matter.
It was 8th place.
I think it could be so much higher.
Yaba Private.
Yabba yabba private.
What is it?
Grandpa's grandfather.
I'm smiling.
I've become a grandfather," he said.
You're smiling, aren't you?
Then 7th place.
But if this lineup,
Isn't it right here in Sense?
It's a loud aation.
Private cake also.
7th place.
Outing with Arline.
Yay.
Very high up.
Isn't this pretty high up?
I thought you were going this way.
Amazing.
That's the top one.
I thought you were not going to say this.
I don't know.
More, don't you have a lot of pretty high-ranking ones in your business?
Yes, it is.
I thought if that happened, I would have to put them here.
This one is my voice.
What?
ONE PIECE, right?
No, Aryn's is better.
I'm not so sure about that either.
Correction then.
Correction.
Shall I put it in again?
7th place.
I don't want to say.
Well, I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
No, no, no.
ONE PIECE official YouTube.
Amazing thing.
Because, already, Hammar, now in 10th place, is now in 11th place,
What, what, what, what?
It's just amazing how much they rank here.
10th place.
I thought it was 10th, but it's not yet.
But you know, flowers have always been my favorite ONE PIECE.
It was a dream.
It's a long-held wish, isn't it?
Yes, it's a long-held wish. It's really ONE PIECE's formula now.
This is already a woman recognized by ONE PIECE.
I don't know about that.
Even if you don't read it every week, yes, you're allowed.
It's not the right way to put it.
Wait a minute.
Not good. I'm off this week.
But you won't read it next week. I'll read it. You won't, will you? I will. You're not following next week, are you?
I'm a little out of track. It's the last time this year, so get along. Please don't do that again. Be nice to each other.
I can't follow it. My mom told me not to change jumps. My mom told me.
Banned? I'll just assemble them and say it. Hey, it's great that you can go out to that frame, isn't it? Yes, it is. Thankfully.
And it's kind of awesome. What? You've been saying you want to sing the theme song for One Piece. All this time.
Many of the One Piece theme songs are sung by Avex. But this time, a non-Avex company sang the theme song for One Piece.
Really? Yes, it is. Who is it?
You can go to Amefura, too. Who? Segawa-san, for example.
Possibilities are emerging. I want to do it, I want to do it. Let's do it.
So, let's do our best. But yuzu, it's Detective Conan. I can't betray him a bit, you know.
Can I ask the three of you to sing together? Yuzukin can't betray me after all.
Let's do Conan too. When he said he couldn't betray us. Let's do Conan too. He's still Detective Conan, so I can't betray him.
Having said all that, Iras is a hot topic right now, and I wanted to do Yuyu Swan, too.
You like it? I love it. I used to watch it all the time, so much so that I neglected my homework and had it taken away.
Yuzu-chan, it's you or George the monkey. I'm definitely not looking at you like that.
Am I looking at you more? Am I looking at you more?
You are totally monkey George. I've got that. I can sing.
What are you up to today? Adventures? Friends? Let's go.
Departing with George. I can sing for fun.
There are a lot of them. Do you see it? I don't have a name.
Fujii Geiraku Oza. With that, I think Yufinios.
I love it. There's a squirrel in the punch. Opening.
Definitely an opening. Because that's the only one that comes up in the market.
Love it. Such a song.
This kind of thing is a rocket. A ragged effect with a large lack of garbage, etc.
New animal species. Hakena. Sazo horinerio.
Janjan travel sami.
I'm saying there's no scale.
I wish I could have told you it was stitching when I said that.
Sweet potatoes. Flowers for rehearsal.
One con land, glu nai. Alohaumonrai.
Wami chiki chiki.
I'm saying there's no scale.
I miss it. Nice, indeed.
Let's aim for Shirai Ka of ONE PIECE.
Yes, it is.
I loved it.
Great. Love it.
It's really great.
If Aira goes to something too, it will be tomorrow.
I'm not sure.
Because they all went.
What about the media type here?
No private life? No.
There is only one, but what the heck, it's probably out of range too. It's out of range.
Uh, this? Yes.
That's good. Oh, it's this way.
That's not private. It's not private when you're playing with the members.
Work, eh? I thought you were a work-related person. No, no, no.
I thought it was private. No, no.
This is work. You and Moeka are drinking alone, right? We're work friends. It's not private.
I thought it was very private. Have you been drinking?
Do you think it will go in the gallery? George, private iris.
It's like entertainment, right? Entertainment, well, well, well, well.
Which? It's not for money. Which one?
Oh, Ira is Moehana's. Yes, she was entertaining Moka. I was entertaining Moeka, too.
That's how it is, isn't it?
That's what I mean. Then you are 7th, not 6th. If there is nothing private.
Okay then? Mine. Private? It's a private matter.
No. 6, I finally got a contact with Kanako. We were able to exchange.
Isn't that private, too? What is it? What is it? That's my job.
I think Kanako probably exchanged as part of her job. We also talked a little about our private lives.
But if Ira were a civilian, he probably wouldn't have exchanged it, so it would be a business story. Right. Because if Ira hadn't come into the industry in the first place.
Okay then, fine, let's talk about work. As work. I exchanged contact information with Kanako as part of my job.
Good for you. Congratulations. Sixth place. You're about that low.
Congratulations. Yes, it's something that's really been a constant contact over the years, like when we got together at that lower plastic festival or something,
That's exactly what we did at the Meiji-za Theater with each member,
When I was going to follow you, I thought it would be nice to exchange contact information. I had been thinking about it for a long time, but I never approached him myself,
I had been taking the same names with them, but I couldn't take the first step and ask them to exchange contact information with me,
But I was finally able to exchange it at the last staple festival. Congratulations!
I was so happy. I'm glad. I gave you a sweater.
I gave him a sweater.
Ko-chan, you can't speak, can you?
No! No, no, no, no! No, no, no! That wasn't the time! Don't you remember!
Same day, right?
Yes.
Same day. I see.
I gave it to you, so you should replace it.
No, it's not! The doctor said please.
Don't do that.
Poor thing.
I'm going home. I'm going home.
That's a bit of a problem.
It's going to lose viewers.
No, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop.
You sent it first?
I will send that to you properly.
It is.
Why did you send it?
Aira.
You should see it.
I'll show you.
I won't show you!
Show me.
It's such a private thing.
Let me see.
I will see to it.
It's my job.
Speaking.
Me, fair and square, they beat me at bull wrestling, and I just got the exchange.
So it's not private. It's a project.
That's him. Go to Karuizawa.
Don't come back from Karuizawa.
Come on, Moka, let's go together.
Don't go.
It will be served at Yuzushi.
But, Moeka's is not served by Yuzu, we just have to serve it.
Weak, already.
Which is weak.
That guy, because there's only one that I can't get out.
Episodes that can't be released.
There's a lot of Moeka, is that okay?
I have a lot of moehana, I have a lot in my photo folder.
Guys, I had a trump card: a yuzu funny face.
I'll get you out.
Are you okay?
It's okay, I'll give you this funny look.
Then they'll know where you live.
They'll know where you live.
What I am sending is too gross.
Oh man, it's okay.
I want to see it.
The first is gross.
We didn't have that exchange.
I won't show you Kanoko's place like that. Then. It's okay, it's private.
Yuzu looks totally similar.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
If anything, it's a little refreshingly simple.
No, I didn't want to be attracted to something, so I didn't want to be too gory.
But really, more,
I definitely think you can put a heart or something on it.
I like this kind of thing more Kanoko, and this kind of thing more Kanoko,
Anko (bean paste) is put on these places,
I really wanted to be like Kanoko,
At that time, Kanoko's staple festival,
See, I got more into it,
I wanted to send a lot of things that were really cute and stuff like that,
I quit.
Because,
From a research student,
I would be happy if I said that this part of Aira-chan is very good.
Glad to hear it.
Do you want me to send it to you?
It's embarrassing.
It was very, very simple.
I don't know, but it's written right.
This, oh man, this stamp.
What? Why, why, why?
That stamp is bad before this.
That's not good.
I'm sending you this.
It's crazy.
You should be more concerned about stamps than that.
Stamps are nothing like that.
The stamps are,
Send all of Momokuro's lines with Momokuro's stamps,
All the lines with Mr. Orca are stamped with Orca's stamps and so on.
But this is good.
You don't know which stamp to use.
What? !
I'm sure he would be happy if he used it.
He uses a stamp that looks like a super funny face.
I don't understand.
I knew it, Momokuro's stamp,
Since it's Mr. Momokuro, why not use his stamp or something?
No, no, no.
With a regular stamp.
Why don't you just use a regular cute stamp?
Is there something really weird in there?
Then I want to cancel the transmission.
I can't do it anymore.
Better to like the stamp than the text.
There is this deletion.
From myself.
How many transmission cycles? Within how many days?
Like within a day.
It has a record.
It's too late.
I didn't understand the meaning of the last one the most.
Yes.
This is bad. I'm already blocked. So she thinks I'm a pain in the ass?
I thought. I thought, I thought. Oh man, this guy's block.
Kanako, you are not like that.
Worst.
It really takes me about 20 minutes to think of one sentence. It's not a sentence.
It's not a sentence. I was fine with the text. I wish you could have seen it. The rock sample was too much.
Will you put it out someday? I won't. I don't want to bother Kanako-chan. I don't want to bother Kanako-chan.
Here's a sample. I'm glad you're Kanako-chan.
I'm a gentle kanako. I would block it if I were you.
Worst. He's the worst senior. I'll tell you one thing.
You should scrub everything that comes in. Why?
Yuzu, my cell phone broke and all the LINEs from Reni-chan disappeared.
What?
It happens, doesn't it? That's for sure. That's not good.
My talk history wasn't backed up, so it's all gone.
All my memories are gone. I exchanged with Shiori before.
You haven't been able to do it? Aylin told me to ask you.
Why don't you just ask them? Just ask now. No, no, no. Great.
Just be coy and ask. Like, "I want Shiori's.
Like I'm using Ailin. Sorry. I would like to see Shiori.
I want to say it when I see you.
You should have gone to Cork village to see the flowers. I would have gone there to exchange them. I hate it so much.
But there's Momoi's singing contest, right? Yeah.
I'll check it all out at Damejame in the new year. I'll check it out at Damejame in the new year.
Yes, it is.
Can you ask her if Hiroshima was exchanged properly or can you ask her for a stamp?
They confirm? They will check.
Oh, no. Oh, no. He's going to announce it.
Who did you end up toasting Yuzu with first?
I want Momokuro's line too.
What? Do you have it, Rin-chan?
I don't have it.
You don't have it?
No one has it.
Arin, Arin has it.
So you could definitely exchange Hanno even on January 19.
I knew it was there that I became ochikazuki, ochikazuki.
But, ochikazuki.
We can put out a song that burns, the game is on.
I'm busy.
I imagine he had his cell phone with him the whole rehearsal at Ailey's. If he had his cell phone, Mr. Black and White would have been able to see him.
Ailey is gal minded.
The sixth place was like
Let's go to Amefura now.
Okay, let's go that way.
I only have three more and one more to go.
We're in 5th place, right?
Maybe we can spread the word with a buzz.
5th place!
Yes.
Abefurachan buzzed!
Yay!
This year?
TikTok.
Do you really feel it?
I can say this now because I have a real feeling about it.
Yes, I think so.
I am ashamed to say.
But the first buzz didn't really feel that great.
Yes, there wasn't much.
At what point do you think, "Oh, we're buzzing?
Attracted customers. Visible, increased numbers.
And work. Content and so on.
Something until now,
We also had the opportunity to perform at festivals that we had never been able to attend before, such as Lucky Fest, Samaste, etc. We were allowed to perform at the All-out Time with the four of us.
I wasn't invited. Yes, and I was also invited to appear on the show, and so on,
Your work has changed a lot. The number of jobs has increased.
I'm happy. I'm feeling it because I've been working a lot more. You have more work outside of your idol work, haven't you? Yes, yes, yes.
Also, when I go to festivals, I'm getting more and more "idol-chan" comments. It's true, I'm getting more. I didn't have that before.
Teri. What do you look like? In times like that, I knew Ira would be next to me,
After all, I want to know if Ira approached you. Because this banquet merry.
Why? It's like, "Ira is there.
I'm pretty sure that's true. People aren't doing it. They're doing it.
But you know, all Amefurasshi, they all have, what do you call them?
You're so hot. The way you look at me. Stop being so crazy.
Don't be so crazy. Your eyes, they're not soft.
Yes, indeed. Indeed.
That sounds a little scary, doesn't it? But that being said, I have one thing to say.
If anything, it's Moeka and Yuzuko who have soft eyes, right? Yes, they are.
But idols are not popular, are they? No, they don't.
I have never met an idol and heard her say she is Moeka or Yuzu Kiyoshi. I've never heard of them.
Not once, right? You two Kamite over here. You greet them every time.
Then it goes like, um, I like you. Like, thank you.
Then one of the kids did the same, and when they started taking pictures,
Oh, every time I say if you like a girl, please go, this way.
Heh.
Yes, it is.
I knew it, but idols are usually, you know, how do you say it?
There are a lot of cute, achie-like girls, right? Yeah.
So I don't know if that makes you want to go this way.
It's shaky, isn't it? Hey.
Jello wants to be popular with idols. What are you going to do?
Bring it up to the cool hairs. You can't.
It's impossible. Absolutely impossible.
It's amazing. Impossible task.
With a medium wife and sweets. Behind the scenes. I greet them myself before I greet them, and then I greet them later as candy flashes,
They asked us to answer if we had a guess, and we would definitely have a reason. I gave him a waiver of sweets and the four of us, nice to meet you.
Oh no. That's a guess, or a rare one.
But you know, I think I'm a good breakup of people like that. The type. The faces?
So if they like cool, they get two, and if they like pretty, they get two,
You mean different types? Amefurasshi has a good balance. If you divide them into many types, they are like this, but if you divide them into smaller types, they are all different.
You mean they're all different?
No, no, no. I hate the same people. What do you say?
I understand. I understand. Even if you divide the Japanese people into 5 or 10 parts, they all enter different parts.
I guess 10 divisions are indeed together. Ten minutes is just about the same.
No, no, no. 50% together, sure.
50% together. Separate when divided into 10 parts.
Then separate. Eight is eight.
You don't have to ride it, and there's nothing to ride.
What is it?
I'm curious. I'm curious. I'm curious.
8 can be.
Oh!
So it's 8...if you divide it into 8 parts, everyone would be in pieces. Ugh!
Ugh!
What is it? It's true.
Okay...I only have 10 minutes.
Why did you start it 9 minutes ago?
If the 5th place is divided into 8 parts, they all fall apart.
No no no. It was a buzz.
Buzz.
I see.
I don't need an orchestra or anything, now.
4th place. I'm very happy.
Let's see, wait for Josho.
Glad to hear it.
What do you say?
Yeah.
Like, like.
In fourth place, we were allowed to do the ceremonial feeding ceremony.
Glad to hear it.
This is the greatness that comes in fourth place.
Or even first place.
If we cut these places off, they'd all be in first place.
I don't want to find it.
We just need to lower Mr. Suzuki's Hanyu Maru-chan.
No, you can't.
Hanyumaru was there.
I also have a reunion with my grandfather.
Ninth place and that's it.
I don't know why it's in there.
I've never had a job like this before.
Glad to hear it.
Because you can do it for the rest of your life or not.
That's right. Glad to hear it.
I had the impression that TikTok was more about the members themselves than about the buzz,
As for the formula feeding ceremony, we had a song used,
Because that's where the connection came from,
It's a connection with the song,
I was happy about that, too.
I really thought it was a good thing I was there to showcase my tansy at the time.
I'm glad You Can Do It was in the lyrics.
Really. But there's always You Can Do It next year.
Yes, yes. The theme is We Can Do It.
We Can Do It.
It will be the same way.
Yes, yes.
So maybe we'll have them continue to use them next year.
By all means.
Best regards.
And I was really happy,
Ira nice pitching and all.
Nice pitching.
Early's.
I was really very nervous,
But even before it started, there were baseball players and Orix-san watching us around quite a bit,
Everyone was so nice to me afterwards,
It was a great relief.
Hey. I'm glad.
It was really good.
At the front, saying it was good.
What if I really don't get it?
Who did you owe thanks to? This is.
Thanks to our members.
That's right.
Yup. It wasn't because the members had their backs to the wall or anything.
If they weren't there.
What if we weren't there?
I couldn't throw it.
That's right.
He was really helpful in a way, but he kept saying he was hungry all the time, and I was nervous, but I was. I was so nervous.
Well, but the sweets in the dressing room were delicious, weren't they?
That was delicious.
Everyone put out their hand right away.
They had prepared a huge amount of sweets, but by the time I left, I was already done.
Almost none. Almost none.
Backstage.
That was delicious.
But really, you made me a uniform.
I'm so happy.
Glad to hear it.
You want to cherish it for the rest of your life, don't you?
And cute. I was really happy.
It was a good experience. I hope to be invited back next year.
Yes, I will do my best. I will do my best.
I will do my best.
Best regards.
Next time, go straight.
3rd place followed by.
3rd place.
Yes.
Free la?
Yeah.
Free Live.
Yes.
We had 500 and 1,000 people, and we achieved both.
Yay.
Wow.
Glad to hear it.
Yeah.
This is.
What is it?
The goal of 500 people was set for the free live coffee event, and the final day was in Toyosu, and the goal was to gather 500 people in Toyosu. 734 people exceeded that goal.
They were reluctant to say 500 people.
Yes.
I thought, "What am I going to do?
We definitely need to get together.
That's what I thought.
I said I didn't want to tell you.
You said.
Oh no. Those times.
I guess I said it here.
I said.
Glad to hear it.
You were pretty scared, weren't you?
I was scared.
I thought I definitely shouldn't do that.
No more until the very last minute before leaving the stage.
Even when it came out.
The staff knows that. The staff doesn't know if it will go to 500. If it doesn't go to 500, I'll do something to make it 500.
It's like handing them out to people you don't even know anymore.
I'm probably already like counting the people on the rooftop, and I'll make it 500 somehow.
I was also told to feel like everyone was already at ease, but it's more than that.
Below.
Not that kind of effort properly, but those who really gathered. Counting.
Gutsy.
It was a stiff 734 people.
Glad to hear it.
I was really happy. But then, during the next free live tour, they set a goal of over 1,000 people on the last day in Toyosu.
Because it's twice as much and it's coming twice as fast. Isn't that bad?
It's great.
No idea.
Yu's personal belongings.
I really didn't like it. I really didn't like it.
1,000 is really not possible.
It's four digits. No, it's not. Because I've never collected four-digit arquists, even for a one-man show.
Yes, it is.
Oh no.
As a subferapty.
It's the first time we've had that many people.
Largest scale.
That's what they call a free live concert.
It wasn't so much that you set a goal and achieved it, was it? That's right. You always ended up feeling a little vague at the end. It was like you couldn't do it.
We have already achieved that twice in a row, and sold out the Bio Site and Shinagawa Stellar Ball this time as well.
Four sold-outs in a row now, or rather, that's what we're accomplishing. It's charming. It's too charming. It's never happened before.
I always regretted that I couldn't sell out the show, even though I enjoyed the show.
It's amazing that there isn't one there. Fun. Really fun.
Here's the thing, I want to keep my head up and do better.
Let's do our best.
The sight, you know, it will remind everyone a little bit.
Yes, that picture is really great, the group photo.
It's amazing, compared to what we had at 3BG, and when we compared and looked at it together, it was a huge increase.
The old group photo, we've been doing this for a long time.
It's always been a sacred place there.
Because sometimes it's really scanty. Some of those are on TikTok, too, you know.
Like the one they used to do in the old days of the scuzzy Toyosu. Like the scuzzy one I did when I was doing the candyflash,
I heard that there were not many people at the stairway. You have never taken a group photo before, have you?
Because there are no people. There are no people, we can't get together.
We decided that we would not take pictures unless we reached our goal, so it was nice to be able to take pictures both times and keep them.
Thank you. Thanks to all of you.
Second place?
Did you just say third place?
2nd place.
Second place
What! We've made it overseas!
This, you know, was one of my goals for this year, so I guess it's pretty big.
I went to Thailand in February for something, and, wow, I went to Taiwan twice for a music video shoot and twice for a festival,
I'm so happy you're going to Malaysia August.
Can you believe this is the first year I've been abroad? It was a long time ago.
You get to go abroad four times in one year. That's really surprising, isn't it?
I am really happy, and we had always talked about the possibility of performing overseas as well,
I am very grateful that we were able to perform overseas in the form of festivals, even though it was not our own mothers,
I can find differences between Japan and other countries,
I was also able to realize that people accept music that makes it rain,
I think it was a very good overseas expansion for us.
It was fun to be abroad in a place that was not a private concert.
Because we won't be playing together abroad for the rest of our lives.
But I want to go to Australia or something with everyone. Or Korea.
I want to go there, but it will never happen. I want to go, but it will never happen.
If I could use teleportation or something, I'd totally go.
Can I have some more time to hang out with the members?
You're making it.
I'm making it, though.
I'm making it, but then, it's not good to be in Osaka.
Because if the four of us are together, we can have fun wherever we go.
So you don't have to go far to enjoy the parks around there as much as you do in Australia.
Honestly.
Karaoke is fun.
Right? That's right.
But I will go abroad with four people and cause such happenings as Yuzu getting lost and not being found.
Sad.
Sorry, but I can't say it best, so I'm lost abroad.
I don't see any strays.
There is absolutely no such thing.
Mr. Suzuki.
I want to make everyone laugh about such happenings as losing a passport or having one's wallet snatched.
Lost is likely to be Anchan.
Hana and Moeka would definitely get lost.
We went somewhere together, and I said, "Where am I?
Yuzu wallet and graze.
Yuzu, you know, the kind that gets rubbed.
And even if it's a little bit of a scam, I'm going to get my hands on it at the same time.
Oh, he said, let's go by cell phone.
It's not something.
So, her face.
You're in first place.
That's what we're doing now.
What do you mean?
You seem to be saying.
Indeed.
But I'll be going to Thailand again next February, and I'd love to go back next year for more.
I want to go. More and more.
I'd like to get out to Asia, too.
I'd like to go outside of Asia, too.
Yes, yes.
I would like to go there.
Are you going to Brazil?
Oh no.
Distant.
I'd like to go there, though.
Next to me, really.
Wanted.
Really.
Really, if you decide to go to Brazil, I'm glad you're already there because you're a real sister.
Oh no.
Don't.
I want you to be whoever you want to be.
Yay.
Don't.
Stop it, that's amazing.
Stop that feeling.
Yuzu and it will be.
Yay.
True, but isn't it a bad idea to push things like that?
I'm pushing it, so it's good to be on top of it.
Then let's do a bleep bleep who you want to be.
Who do you want to be?
Pippy.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Uh, how long? How long is the flight?
It takes a lot of time because of connections and so on.
Can we go to L.A.? L.A.? Almost a day?
There is a transfer loss.
Isn't there a difference between a 1-hour member and a 12-hour member?
No, it's not.
24 to 26 hours.
Yes, one more day.
Oh no!
It's impossible.
I'm sorry but I don't want to be any member.
I honestly don't like any of the members.
I'm sorry, but or I can't say it best, that's it.
I don't like it either. Let me tell you that I don't like it either.
Because I have the authority.
Authority.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
What should I do?
It's about which one is better.
I thought, "Is this person good?
If it was this person, I would feel safe for a day.
It doesn't matter which one.
Even on airplanes.
Yes.
Think about sitting on a plane for a day,
It's about where you shoot.
One more.
I definitely need to set up someone with the members.
Yeah.
Tough.
But I have two choices. I have two choices. I feel sorry for the one choice.
You don't have to worry about that.
Yes, well, let's see.
What?
Everyone, YES.
Why?
YES is just fine. Maybe.
They are great, they joke around a lot when they joke around, and they talk to each other.
I think they would joke about eating dinner or waking up,
But you want proper alone time, too.
So we can naturally take the time to do that properly.
From Kojima's point of view.
I'm an IRA, you know, because I'm coming from here, from the IRA.
I, I don't want to come, so it's like, hey, that's not right.
With Moka, it's probably fun at first.
But then Moeka started to get annoyed with Hana,
I think I'm going to start getting kind of angry. Maybe.
I had a feeling that was the case. Moka stopped.
Moka is like, really, stop it already. I'm going to start saying it's boring already,
No, right?
No, you can't.
I want to stand up. From the chair.
Okay.
What, can I ask you to stand up for a second?
It was a bit of a hassle to go there, every time I had to knock myself out, too.
Simply.
Oh, like doing the rear one at a time?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, and by process of elimination, it's yuzu, although yuzu probably becomes annoyed and annoyed about flowers in the process,
Because that annoyance is funny.
You mean they think it's funny to be annoying?
Because I want to bully the annoying with it.
I say it's because it's annoying.
But since the result is this.
It's because we are in love with each other.
Over there.
I always feel sorry for Moyaka.
What?
I talk to them about this or that, even if it's not important.
I talk to Moayaka quite a bit.
Because I want to talk so much.
But I always take the earphones out every time and ask, "What? What? He always does everything for me.
When I talk, they answer.
So, the process seems tedious, and you don't want to be stopped in the middle of a drama or listening to music, do you?
So, I'm sorry.
So I didn't choose it.
The nerve to talk to someone with earphones is amazing.
Yeah.
I want to talk.
I want to talk normally.
But, it's fine, but I'm not going to do that next to someone who is watching a movie with headphones on.
More than being spoken to.
It is a bit more of an eyesore than being spoken to.
Don't you understand? How do you think people watch movies on airplanes with earphones?
I see it when I see it.
I'll look at it, Aina.
I see when I see.
It's just you for a day, about 26 hours.
Me, after much thought, I'm not so sure about flowers either.
Flowers are serious, because they look like they really don't want to.
But, Hana, he said he would play with me all the time without headphones on.
So,
But wait, this is something, you know, different, yes, significant.
You say you don't like it when they come over. But if I don't go, they probably won't talk to me.
You keep saying that. You've been bullying me.
You're bullying.
What are you talking about? Hana, when Aina started watching movies, you always interrupted her thinking, "What is this person doing?
Yes, you're interrupting me so much.
So, it was interesting to see the swooning.
I am not having fun.
Yeah, that's good.
I, for one, would like to go abroad next time.
Oh no!
Better to say.
Because, you know, over here, I'm not having fun, then.
If I try to have fun, you won't have fun.
But when flowers try to have fun, I don't have fun.
Give and take. With a revival.
At one time.
Reanimation.
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no.
Over and above the order.
This is the sneakiest thing I've ever seen.
You'll be back alive and in turn, you'll be back in order.
Over the order by reviving.
Then, he said, it would be better for the three of us to go over the order.
No, no, no.
So, properly, only one of them is fun.
It should be done for every transfer.
It should be changed with each transfer.
What do you mean?
I don't care anymore.
Okay, okay, I know the solution. Why don't we just sit in the middle four seats?
Then I want the middle, the middle.
Just the edge.
Of course, it can be a monocoque.
Wow.
Yes, payback.
Next to four, four seats for the plane.
In the middle, in the middle, yada, yada, yada.
If the edges are good, let's do like Hanahira's in the middle already.
No, but no. I want the edge. I want the edge, but you don't want these two next to you.
Oh no, no, but okay.
But if I do, won't you talk to me?
Hey, screw it, I'm talking to you.
I watch movies.
I talk to them.
It gets in everyone's way.
Watching movies.
If it were,
There were four seats in the middle, right?
There it is, there it is.
MV return.
In the end, Hana and Moka were very noisy.
Yes, Moehana is incredibly picky when it comes to flowers.
So, okay, good for you, but yuzu,
But not in Brazil.
Yuzu, Airaka Hana.
No, if it was Brazil, it's really love well and good.
Why? I don't think it bothers me much, most of all.
Absolutely, I'll do this.
Aira: Okay, okay, solved.
Just Aira, no more, like first class.
What's that, I'm all alone and boring.
Then once, we once.
That is first class.
You're boring all by yourself.
I don't have that kind of money.
What's that, three people flying together?
After all, it's three against one.
First Class.
Oh, no.
You want a discussion.
I don't want to go first class.
Something, if you want first class.
I want to talk about it.
Oh no, oh no, because you're all alone.
Alone, like this, gracefully.
It's 24 hours.
It's 24 hours, right?
Meals will also change.
Then it's not first class at all.
Amazing.
Because I can't. I can't not talk to people.
I want some alone time, though.
Okay, okay.
Aira, I'll give up first class now.
Yield.
Who would you give it to?
This, this.
That's terrible. Oh, no.
No good, to Moka.
Eeeeeeee!!!
But I'm already thankful for Moehana.
Thanks, I'll have them say that.
Moehka, already, put on your earphones.
I don't want it, Moehana.
One, different, different, different.
Okay, totally.
Not at all, I liked the way you said it.
You can go first class.
Yuzu also wanted to be thought of as unwanted.
No, something different, something different.
You don't need it.
Don't.
Don't say it like that.
But Moka is.
Yuzu, too, is an unwanted selective inclusion.
I said I was talking to him.
The way you put it, it makes it worse.
Poor thing.
A little bit, if you get annoyed.
I don't remember being annoyed, though.
Something like, hey, earphones.
Then I'll go first class.
It's not fair.
I'm so, so happy.
First class, then.
First class please.
No way.
What should I do?
No one is watching.
No one will see it.
Moka, you were in the middle.
Me, first class, yuzu middle please.
For me, though, it's really hell.
Yes, that's enough.
I was told, "This way, like this.
Hell.
No, but I get it.
Then I can do it, you know, in front of the bathroom or something.
Then, well, wait.
If I don't have this, will I move up in the rankings?
Nope.
So, this and the rest.
Oh, I can't do it anymore.
Without it, would the ranking go up?
If it doesn't, it will go up.
That, I can put up with.
I'll be patient.
That's what you did in Malaysia, and now you're trying to put up with it in Brazil?
I didn't think that was bothering me yuzu.
Very, very bad.
The staff, the staff next to me, was really bad.
He says, "Hmmm.
Uchiru, that was super awkward, wasn't it?
Loudly, he's saying something.
Bigger.
What is it?
Eh, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then, then I'll figure it out on my own. Good luck with this one.
Oh no, do it far away.
Sorry, sorry.
So, let's win the majority again.
That's enough.
No, I want to move up the pecking order, guys, guys. If I have to put up with that.
So, even if you do put up with that, you're in second or third place, and if you can't put up with that, you're in second or third place, so now you guys are not going home.
He's in first place?
Yes, it is.
Bye-bye.
Why?
Because there is no second place.
With the fear of second place, you are not out of first place.
It takes two.
I'm starting to be able to say that, so it's pretty exciting when we talk.
Hey, it's a lot of fun, isn't it?
It's nice.
It's quite fun.
He says he doesn't enjoy being with me.
Wrong.
Oh my God, that's my line.
It's my line the most.
Jealousy, too much woman. It's my line, the best.
What do you mean? Really.
Really, she's a jealous woman.
Don't get excited without me.
Oh, oh, oh.
Are you telling everyone?
It's the last rain talk of the year.
Someone should choose Aira, right?
What is it? I won't choose. I won't choose even if you put the staff in.
I wasn't chosen either.
No flowers were chosen either. Rest assured.
No, no, no, if you put one-chance flowers in the staff, maybe they will be chosen.
Maybe?
They said they wouldn't be chosen even if I put in a staff member. I don't know. Maybe Mr. Morimichi will choose me.
I'm not listening.
You get to choose.
I just hid it in an air pot.
Ears.
I'm pretending I'm working.
Yes.
Oh, God, seriously. Oh, no more. So that's what it looks like.
I'm already depressed. She's depressed. Hana-chan is.
Why, because it is the same as Yuzu's.
Try Okinawa first, then.
Even Okinawa is about 2 hours away?
Then, the ranks of the accumulators will go up ridiculously.
So, there, I couldn't hold back there either. It was the end. That's why.
Okay, then. I've been doing this for a long time now.
Eh, so Okinawa.
I'll be at nothing. I'll be at nothing.
If it were in Okinawa, anyone might be fine.
That's the short time you have.
Yeah.
Well, on the other hand, you might not like it even in that short time, right?
If it were these two.
How can we spend time without harm?
It is.
Then yuzu, Okinawan flower might be good.
Why?
Because I think it will do the most harm. In a few hours.
On the contrary.
A smile, even for two hours.
He wanted to try it.
It's going to interrupt your smile.
Then why don't you just sit in the middle, Yuzu?
I don't want to.
Want to give it a try?
Thank you.
Once.
1 time.
But I probably wouldn't really do any harm, if it was for two hours.
Yes, if it was two hours, maybe that.
Harmless.
But I think the most sobering harm is Moeka.
For example, if you are seated with two people and there is no one to talk to. If you have no one to talk to, you would probably put on earphones.
Indeed.
So, a little nasty harm.
A little nasty harm.
Because, you don't have to speak here and there.
Yeah.
If it comes down to it, no harm, no harm.
NO.
Then no.
I'm not sure what's going on. I don't know what's going on.
Yuzuki and Moeka don't have to speak at this time today.
Either one is fine.
I'll talk alone.
The two little ones are still not good enough to talk, but someone has to mess with them. That's not the best part.
Yes.
But since they want to be let out, it means that there is no one who wants to be let out right now.
Yeah.
We need to go without recruiting members who want to be served.
New Member.
New Member Application Requirements.
Someone who wants to be messed with.
What do you mean?
Arima is coming.
Yes, yes, yes. That was Arima.
Arima.
I don't have a partner.
Already there? Let's give it a try.
No partner.
Isn't this a point of improvement for next year?
Sure. I have to say No. 1.
Oh my God, how much did we talk about this?
It's true.
It was a bit tough, wasn't it?
But I think the first place is obvious.
Yes.
It is 2023.
Then the first place goes to
Batgirls story a great success
Great!!! I'm not finished, though. No, I already do. It's definite.
I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it, and I want to do it!
The tension is very different from what I heard at the opening. No, but that is because we have to be perfect by the time the show starts, even though I am worried now.
I shouldn't, already. I have to! I have to do it even if I, you know, don't make it or can't do it in time or something.
Then, if this is not in time, I can't say that with confidence, but it's not that we're not in time, it's that we don't have confidence in ourselves.
I think we can make it better and better. I want to push them. I want to push it.
I want to push myself. I'm talking about "cornering myself," so cornering. We're all so serious, we're all so amazing. But isn't this pretty much how rehearsals go? Well, yeah.
So, I feel like my confidence is, how do you say it? Nothing. Nothing.
Nothing, nothing. Already,
I can show good things, but I want to make them better. That's right. Yes, I do.
And Kojima-san is alone. Why is he all alone? You don't know until the day of the event. I don't know.
Everyone suddenly. You might get a fever. Suddenly, you might go on an overseas business trip or work. You have to put in Zusi.
Zusi. To Dubai. I'm going back to Dubai. I'm going back to Dubai. Well, that's some kind of zooey.
Then it's some kind of zooey. Something that came in. There was a tip-off. Mr. Suzuki, Hamhar-chan.
Hamhar-chan. Yes, Hamuharu-chan. I'm going to have to go looking for you. Don't you want to run away? Go to your room, take a walk in your room and run away.
Leave it to Mom. I have to leave it to you to look for it, after all. I'll just wait for her to come back.
But that's really the point. It's the total sum total of 2023 with all the activity, isn't it? Yes, it is.
21 is. Yeah. You can't fail, right? I can't. I won't. I won't. You can't fail. Yeah, you're a lout. Yeah, you're a lout.
Or harvested, maybe. I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm happy, really. I'm really looking forward to it. As I said in the opening, really. A great success.
We will give you the best live performance and you will not regret coming, so I hope you will enjoy the show as much as you can.
Please. I will do my best.
Are you okay? No, it's bad. I get that kind of anxious feeling.
Wouldn't it be nice to have a feeling of insecurity? You feel down once every time, don't you?
We're going through one depression. I'm already depressed today.
You guys should be depressed once.
After that, it takes, doesn't it? It's better to get really pissed off once.
I don't know, before, I was always really pissed off before a gig.
Hey. Every time.
I was so pissed off.
But, well, there are some bad things about Jiro.
Yes, we are. We are bad.
Now, though, everyone is starting to get depressed remembering the lesson.
Now.
I found myself with nothing to say.
Today's voice training.
Situation.
I will say it when I remember.
I remember now, don't I?
Can we forget about the delivery?
I've been doing this for a long time.
But somehow the teachers are also telling me that they think there is room for growth,
I know you are telling me this because you feel supported by me,
I'm in the process of accepting that now, still.
I'm in the process of inputting.
It's still a bit of a stretch, though.
It's hard to reverse the situation.
I know,
I wanted to fix that.
So I'm giving input now.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's that time, now.
Yes.
I guess they told me it was too much time to do it.
It's too close to home.
Too recent.
Because it's first.
Because it was a few hours ago.
Tomorrow, there will be a good one.
It's different.
I'm having a down day.
Tomorrow will be good.
I'm looking forward to it, Friday.
I hope you look forward to it.
I'm not sure.
The Amefurasshi 10-episode talk in 2023.
That I was.
Hey, you haven't folded it in yet, have you?
2023.
No, but there are so many that I haven't really mentioned.
There are a lot of them.
It really is.
There were a lot of besses and such.
There are so many, really.
I really wanted to give him first place, like I took the big prize.
Great pleasure.
I wish I could say I went to Disney 10 times this year or that I was #1.
It's okay.
Sorry, Ara-chan.
It was the first time for Aira and Tomoyuka to meet, and so on.
And the day narrative.
Like the day narrative.
Yes, on the street.
Yes, I think so.
Yes.
Um, there was also Rabbit and Kaya Hamada.
I also got a lot of arias.
There were episodes of Seiya-san and others in the camp.
I'm glad to hear that so many things have happened to you, so many things that you get lost in.
Glad to hear it.
I would like to connect this to next year.
I will do my best.
May we have many more episodes in 24 years.
I'm not sure.
I wonder what it is already, because I think there is already a lot going on at the beginning of the year and through the year-end and New Year's holidays.
Yeah.
We can talk about all kinds of things when the day dawns.
Yes, it is.
There's so much to catch up on.
Dark colors and ameshabe.
Yeah.
Next January.
I'll do ameshabe, but there are lots of events.
Yes.
There are about four events.
About 4 hours.
I think there are about four.
Yes, there is.
One-man, Idol Wave, Halftime Show, Peach Color Dagase.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sure there are some.
Yeah.
Yes.
I mean to see what you have to say in the future.
That's why I want to go to the announcement time, but first I'm going to go now?
Yes.
Jansen.
Here are the fresh photos that will be sold at the Sierra Ball in Shinagawa on December 22.
Yay.
Cool.
Yes.
This is a photo of the costumes used in the music video for the spin.
It's very cool and I hope you can get it if you want.
Please.
He wrote his signature.
Signature written.
I wrote and wrote quite a few names.
Quite a lot.
I think you're right.
So I think it will hit the mark.
Please get one by all means.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Then, I guess that way.
Yeah.
That way, I guess.
We will be performing at Idol Wave in Tokyo on Friday, December 29.
Wow.
Yes.
Tickets are on sale until 23:59 on Wednesday, December 20.
The next three days or two days will be the last idol festival of the year, so please come and visit us. Please come and enjoy the festival.
Please.
On December 30, I will be performing in the halftime show at an Ibaraki Robots home game.
Oooh.
Yes.
Best regards.
It's a great halftime show, and we want to do our best to make it exciting.
Yes, I am looking forward to watching the game next week. I'm looking forward to watching next week. Hey, I'm looking forward to it. Please do.
We will also be performing in the Momoshikida Gassen, which Momokuro-san holds every year.
Thank you very much. This year, we will be at Yokohama Arena, and I think we will be at some of the venues,
Somewhere. Somewhere. Please take a look. Please do.
This is it for the year. Yes. Now, therefore, I would like to finish in this section.
Yes, I am. This week, too, Sui-kun. This is the last episode. No, it's not.
Thank you, Sui-kun. Thank you, Sui-kun. Thank you special.
No, sir. It's the last episode. Thank you Special.
This week, Sui-kun made a line stamp for Sui-kun.
Seriously, it's really bad. It's really bad. It's really bad.
It's not. It's not Sui-kun's video, already.
He made a LINE stamp. He's going to use it a lot.
And all they do is put words that the Kojima family would say on their stamps. That's right.
I thought. You can't advertise the Kojima family, this corner.
Can I afford that? Sales. Only family can afford it.
Sales. Only family can afford it. Is that so?
You could buy a yuzuki, though. If I give it to you.
People who are sent stamps can buy them in the store from there.
Really? Really?
Ah!
Can I buy one? What? I mean, you can buy it, right?
Right? This guy.
Yuzu, you can buy it from here, even if you do it this way.
Really? Here you go.
Oh, he's doing it, he's doing it.
You'd buy it. Oh, I'm doing it.
This, Mr. Kodaira, is the last broadcast at the end of the year, and it has a dark influence. Eh, is this okay?
I don't know what's going on, but I'm operating on my own. Is everything all right?
Eh, no. Signature stamps, you know.
Hey. Yeah. Well, that is, unless someone puts a stamp on it, right?
Yes, yes, yes. So it certainly doesn't show up when you look it up.
So, for example, if a flower were to put a stamp on a junior high school group line, it would mean that all the junior high school students would leave.
Oh, hey. Oh, and you're serving it late next time?
A little bit, um, yes, I could. Yes, I have.
I made a second version of this. What? People don't know about this.
You made it again? I ain't seen it.
Well, well, well...it's not Stardust, Mr. Masu. Well, well, well.
Feel free to do so, though.
Wait a minute...or something like that, I'm sure. I'm sure.
This is how we have a drinking party. You know.
You're definitely a mom now. Or a flower daddy.
Don't use another house or absolutely nothing but flowers anymore. It's backroom business, backroom business.
Dark business. Not black market.
That's no good. And there's a piece of Ron in it.
That's not good, is it? It's not good.
Why? Ron is my dog, too.
It's the last episode.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
The last episode was healing. Please don't let it end.
We look forward to working with you next year in 2024. Next year ?
Watermelon again this week. Next year?
This week?
It will be with Maru Hanyu.
It's a lie.
I don't change my expression the most. I am.
Kevin grows the most from the age of months to one year old, right?
That's the most obvious one, growth.
I wanted to see Kevin, though. I wanted to do it Kevin.
I did go out, though.
This guy was threatening me, saying, "Screw you.
I'm the one who said that.
Like, don't think Kevin thinks he can show up.
Wow.
It's bullying younger kids into junior positions.
You're going to do that? It's bullying junior staff.
I didn't do it because I didn't want anything to happen to Kevin.
I won't do that. To a giant dog like that.
I think I'm going to get hit. Stop with the giant dogs.
It's even called a giant dog to begin with.
I have no love for Kevin.
It's terrible, Kevin.
He got in our car and drooled bam, he was out the door.
It sucks.
Dad was angry.
Hana Papa's face became more and more cheerful.
In our, in my car.
Hana Papa takes good care of his car.
I named it before I replaced it.
Really already.
I'm really, really drooling over Kevin.
I really don't want to be followed when I buy personal clothes or anything,
I said, "Wait," got dressed, and then said, "Yessir, yessir, yessir.
It's tough, that girl.
What's that?
Then 2024.
No, even flowers drool.
Don't put them together.
Well, certainly when I came to stay at Yuzukenchi,
Reri's pillow drooled over me, and I it.
It's just like that.
I'm getting rid of it.
I heard he was drooling in class.
For Kikun.
I'll never spill it," he said,
There is a song about sleeping on Reri-chan's pillow and slobbering on it.
Oh, that.
I'm going to have to settle for Abe-chan.
Yes.
No, it's bad.
Never slobber.
I don't drool anymore these days.
Eh, the other day, gel.
Oh, I drooped.
You drooped.
That's right.
Um, I was looking at my phone, even though I was alone, just doing this normal thing,
It was like a porta-potty, and then it started dripping.
Yeah, yeah.
And this guy spits on me.
It's so, so bad.
Yaba.
No, because they will think you are a dirty woman.
To slobber, to moonlight.
No, it's not.
A little bird. A little bird.
Please don't.
To the size of a small bird.
Small bird size.
Oh, I didn't see it.
Proof that you haven't seen it.
To the size of a small bird.
I haven't seen any candy!
Small bird size.
Not seen.
The size of the little bird is amazing.
I didn't even see the person who just said what that is in the comments section.
The ones you haven't seen.
There's no way I'm looking at it.
Oh, wait. What was that? Drool?
There's no way I'm looking at it!
It's a lie. I'm sorry.
What was that? Drool? A little bird?
Haguki?
Tiny bitterns?
Yuzu?
Debutanabara
Don't.
Not good.
I said it's not good, because Hana named Yuzuki as her line name.
Kotori is the cutest.
cunning and sneaky
Let me put it a different way.
giving one the feeling of
expression
indigo blue make-up used in Kabuki
Worst.
It's a little more than idol-ness.
It's the end of the year.
Next year, I would like to start the year with a cute and idol-like look.
I'm going to change my route.
Next year.
How about we have a championship to see who can be the prettiest at the beginning of the year?
Really?
Don't forget that.
forgetful
Clothes, too.
In high spirits.
I'm just saying she's cute, but she doesn't look good in frilly clothes.
Not really. Sports.
So you're fine with your own style?
If it turns out to be cute.
I like to dress up in my own way.
Like, you're really into it.
You're already fired up!
Bringing the cutest, most enthusiastic cuteness at the beginning of the year.
The dress is
There's room to relax, and we're the best at it right now.
She's got a dress, this girl.
Alumni Association
I bought a dress for the reunion.
more than
The dress came in.
wedding wedding
something or other
I was imagining something like...
And yours.
Dresses like wow!
Because it's online.
Will you come with me then?
So I'm going to Ameshabe.
Looking forward to it.
Who can be the most enthusiastic?
The first No. 1 to get fired up in 2024 is
Can someone please let me know what you all expect to hear?
I forget.
Someone mentions it.
Forgot this one.
Yuzu is cunning in this way.
When you only remember one person, absolutely.
They won't tell me what's going on.
Forget about everyone else.
I think you should get interesting.
Because it's better to forget.
you can't do it!
You ain't gonna teach me that place either.
choreography
That's right, I won't tell you the choreography or the lyrics.
me
I'm going to improvise, I'm going to sakshi.
No, you can't.
But with immediate deployment.
Even if you tell me it was good right away.
No, no, no.
No improvised lyrics.
Also in 2024
Looking forward to it!
Thank you so much Ameshabe 2023!
Thank you very much.
And finally, a little bit, ladies and gentlemen.
Christmas is coming soon.
From Moyaka Santa
Christmas Spell Moe Moe Merikuri in the corner.
I would like to say goodbye.
Yes, sir.
year of the rat
Christmas
hmm
Yeah, yeah.
Don't woo.
Ask him to stop mmming.
It was creepy.
If you put "eo" between "minato" and "eo", it is also "eri" Christmas!
I don't need an explanation or anything.
shall we wrap it up now?
I wish the whole world would do that.
Oh, yeah.
something that should be ignored
Why are you being so nice?
Are you sure you want to do this last Ameshabe?
It's okay, because it's also an Ameshabe.
Well, this is what I'm talking about, which is very Amershabe-ish.
Yes, sir.
Then let's all go together.
heave, ho!
Amenur chumoa mehera chaberry (Amenur chumoa mehera chaberry)
Amershave for short
Thank you for this year
Thank you very much.
bye-bye